That
That was 49 days ago, and now it's like
It's like summer out. It's
It's um
And now Now, 49 days later, now it's uh
It's It's 78°
outside.
It's like the first day of summer.
Fantastic.
Huh.
Thanks, Jordan.
>> No problem, James.
>> Oop.
Oh.
>> So
So the guys at One Wheel called me about
six months ago, and they said they
wanted to make a bike.
This is an e-bike review. I just want to
be super duper clear. This is not a
sponsored video. I'm not paid. This is
not not a sponsored video.
And I'm like, you make the One Wheel.
Why would you want to make a bike?
Uh especially because especially because
the e-bike market is completely
saturated. I personally have one e-bike
that goes 70 miles an hour.
It's awesome. Another e-bike that's like
a BMX e-bike. I popped the tire trying
to bunny hop over a garbage can. It's
awesome. And then one that I got off of
Amazon that's pretty cheap, but I can
like ride my kids on the back.
It's awesome. So then what? Like what
would be the differentiator
to make the One Wheel e-bike
What would the differentiator be to make
this stand out?
And they said to me, "We're going to
make the most fun e-bike." And now fun
is subjective. How
How would you objectively make the most
fun e-bike?
I've been skateboarding
since the early '90s, and I've never
been able to like smoothly do a kickflip
ever.
I've always loved skateboarding, but I'm
absolutely terrible at it. Similar with
never being able to do a kickflip, I've
never been able to do a wheelie. Like,
I've never I've never been able to
really do a wheelie on a bike.
So, that's that's part of the pitch with
this thing. You're supposed to be able
to do automatic
self-balancing
wheelies.
So, this is it. This is me trying to
break a lifetime curse of never being
able to do a wheelie.
Come on.
Definitely takes a little practice.
Starting to get the hang of it.
So, it uses the same balancing
technology, like the gyroscope, that's
in the One Wheel is in the back wheel of
the bicycle.
The dude at One Wheel said, "3 days of
practice before you get it." I'm like,
"3 minutes in."
Ready?
This is the best wheelie I've ever done
in my entire
natural-born life.
What's up?
All right, the wheelie thing is is
outrageous.
Like,
it's not a 3-day learning curve, but
it's definitely not immediate.
But, when you're not when you're not
ripping wheelies like Nitro Circus,
it's just a really fun little bike to
rip around town on.
What qualifies you as an expert wheelie.
Don't break it, please. I'm not telling
you to wheelie.
>> I don't know.
>> Oh, there we go.
>> He's going to He's going to kill
somebody.
>> a waiver? I don't really I don't feel
like we
>> Can you wheelie on that?
>> Yeah.
>> Really?
Want to see?
>> Yeah.
>> Want to see?
>> Don't hurt yourself.
Woo!
Can you wheelie?
>> No, I cannot wheelie.
So, you want to keep your weight in the
front and your elbows bent.
Oh,
Woah!
>> Push the button! Push the button! I
thought we were going to I thought we
were going to lose him.
>> I did, too. You didn't fall. You did
great.
Have a great day, guys.
>> Bye.
So,
is it
is it the most
the most fun
e-bike ever?
>> Um
>> a pretty fun e-bike. And yeah, I think I
started this video with the question of
does the world need another e-bike?
One Wheel I I think you did it. The
world did does need the Antik.
Marlon,
>> Yeah.
>> you want to try my new e-bike?
It does automatic wheelies for you.
>> Yeah?
>> First of all, you have to get a balance.
>> Yes, Marlon.
Looking good, Marlon. You want to try a
wheelie?